Daylan Hoff

Software Engineer

Contact & Info

Salt Lake City, UT (435) 592-5991 daylan.hoff@gmail.com

Website:

www.daylanhoff.com

Linkedin: DaylanHoff

Skills

C++ Open VPN C# Google Cloud .NET Framework Outlook **xUnit** Azure Git **Powershell** Github Java JUnit Cloud Bees **Python** MySal Microsoft SQL **JavaScript** MongoDB **NodeJS ReactJS** Adobe Cloud Rest API **Photoshop RabbitMQ** Illustrator Docker Premiere Pro **After Effects** Ruby Groovy **Acrobats**

IDES

Visual Studio VS Code RubyMine CLion PyCharm InteliJ Eclipse PhpStorm

Environments

Windows 7 - 11

MacOS

Linux

Linux Server

Amazon Workspace

CPanel

Plesk

VMware

Proxmox

References

DevOps Engineer:Justin Johnson - (801) 984-6125

Quality Assurance Engineer: Jared Doerr - (801) 948-6485

Contract Work

Andrew F. Sbarbaro - (331) 235-0000 Kevin Long - (775) 501-2869

Summary

Extensive knowledge with multiple programming languages such as C#, C++, Java, .Net, Python, Node JS, and more. Experience working with and on technical support teams. Team leader effectively able to communicate with others and take charge of problems.

Work History

06-2021 -Current

DevOps Engineer

AdvancedMD, South Jordan - In Person

- Wrote code with Powershell & .NET Frameworks to reduce time spent working with Git to help automate and improve life within the team.
- Utilized what is now known as Cloud Bees & Azure DevOps to effectively roll out product releases.
- Integrated team work skills in order to effectively communicate and produce quality tools with and for foreign and domestic departments.
- Worked with several other departments such as the Quality Assurance department in order to improve workflow and successfully achieve release goals.

04-2021-

Quality Assurance Engineer

AdvancedMD, South Jordan - Remote

- Used Postman to test funtions of the application and reduce bugs.
- Created Unit Tests to help automate and reduce bugs while verifying the integrity of our application.
- Wrote code in the C# .NET Core Framework to implement the Unit Testing.
- Utilized a form of Agile Scrum to effectively communicate and plan with other members of the company.
- Worked with AWS Workspace, and servers to help setup, and automate the creation of other environments.

Contract Work

01-2019-03-2020

Fullstack Developer

Neybyte Software, Seattle - Remote

- Trained Customer Support Agents regarding company operations, policies, and services to insure a customer satisfaction guarantee.
- Worked heavily with Customer Support to fix bugs, resulting in a 40% reduction in customer complains.
- Used Java to create the core front end and back end of the application.
- Scripted with MySQL and other programming languages like python to help query databases and gather data relevant to users.

03-2019-06-2020

Backend Developer

1CmpleteSolution, Reno, - Remote

- Updated existing systems to support modern payment gateways to improve customer experience.
- Trained employees on how to properly utilize the software in order to provide discounts or price adjustments as needed.

Education

12-2021

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Neumont College of Computer Science - Salt Lake City, UT